Finding Aid for the Augustus F. Hawkins papers LSC.1642
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Legislative Files, 1963-1990; (Contained in 39 Boxes)
  - 97th Congress (), 1981-82
    - Committee Files
      - Veterans' Affairs Committee. (Box 18)
      - Ways and Means Committee. (Box 18)
      - Joint Committee on Printing. (Box 18)
    - Affirmative Action Forum. (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence. (Box 18)
    - Legislative Support Organizations. (Box 18)
  - 98th Congress (), 1983-84
    - List of Legislation Bills Sponsored
      - H.R. 5886, American Folklife Preservation Act. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 1036, H.R. 3485, Community Renewal Employment Act (2). (Box 18)
      - H.Res. 13, Contingent Funds for Standing and Select Committees. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 4731, Effective Schools Development in Education Act of, 1984. (Box 18)
      - H.Res. 404, Funding for Investigation and Studies for House Administration Committee. (Box 18)
      - H.Res. 111, House Information Systems Budget. (Box 18)
      - H.Res. 428, Funding for 2nd Session of 98th Congress for HIS. (Box 18)
      - H.Res. 81, Legislative Reorganization Act. (Box 18)
      - H.Res. 63, Members of the Joint Committees on the Library and Printing. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 5017, Youth Incentive Employment Act. (Box 18)
    - Bills Cosponsored
      - H.R. 5231, Academic Equity and Excellence Through Bilingual Education Act of, 1984. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 604, African Refugees Relief Day. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 5264, Agricultural Producers Antitrust Access Act. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 1, Amendment to Constitution, re Equal Rights for Men and Women. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 999, American Conservation Corps Act of, 1983. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 881, American Defense Education Act. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 213, Eubie Blake Day. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 2144, Challenge Grant Amendments of, 1983. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 2624, Civil Rights Amendments Act of, 1983. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 4813, Comprehensive Hazardous Substances Cleanup and Emergency Relief Act of, 1984. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 6210, Comprehensive Nuclear Weapons Freeze and Arms Relations Act of, 1984. (Box 18)
      - H.Con.Res. 160, Condemning Soviet Attack on Korean Flight 007. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 487, D-Day National Remembrance. (Box 18)
      - H.Res. 190, Education Opportunity, Amended. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 3364, Consumer Telecommunications Act of, 1983. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 2090, Economic Equity Act of, 1983. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 5596, Education for Gifted and Talented Children and Youth Improvement Act of, 1984. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 4402, Electric Consumers Protection Act of, 1983. (Box 18)
      - H.Con.Res. 227, Sense of Congress, re Early Projection of Election Coverage. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 1310, Emergency Mathematics and Science Education Act. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 325, Emergency Medicine Week. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 2207, Emergency School Aid Act. (Box 18)
      - H.Res. 513, Energy Tax Credits. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 429, Exchange Student Program Between the U.S. and People's Republic of China. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 1603, Essential Preventive Programs for Children. (Box 18)
      - H.Con.Res. 355, Establish a Commission on Employment Discrimination in the Legislative Branch. (Box 18)
      - H.Con.Res. 226, Expressing Concern for Members of the Baha'i Religion in Iran. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 4642, Fair Insurance Coverage Act. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 5081, Fair Trade in Steel Act of, 1984. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 4367, Federal Election Campaign Act of, Amended., 1971 (Box 18)
      - H.R. 2250, H.R. 4120, Federal Communications Commission Rules (2). (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 383, Florence Crittenton Mission Week. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 5180, Food Stamp Act of, Amended., 1977 (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 2, Freeze on and Reduction in Nuclear Weapons. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 777, Full Employment Work Opportunity Act. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 5084, Hazardous Air Pollutants Amendments Act of, 1984. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 3021, Health Care for the Unemployed Act. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 5240, Higher Education Amendments of, 1984. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 4475, High Technology Research and Scientific Education Act of, 1983. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 2332, High-Technology Training Act. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 4475, High Technology Research and Scientific Education Act of, 1983. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 1030, Home Recording Act of, 1983. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 4440, Human Needs and World Security Act. (Box 18)
      - H.Res. 385, Sense of House of Representatives, re New Interior Secretary. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 3748, Amend U.S. Code, Title 5, re Immigration and Naturalization Service. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 2262, Malt Beverage Interbrand Competition Act. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 800, H.R. 3706, Martin Luther King, Jr. Legal Holiday (2). (Box 18)
      - H.R. 4870, Medicare Solvency and Health Care Financing Reform Act of, 1984. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 5096, Minority Investment Tax Act of, 1984. (Box 18)
      - H.Con.Res. 112, Expression of Congress, re Namibia. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 284, National Aeronautics and Space Administration 25th Anniversary. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 4468, Native American Programs Act Amendments of, 1983. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 526, National Animal Health Week. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 507, National Cerebral Palsy Month. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 445, National Child Abuse Prevention Month. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 386, National Congregate and Meals on Wheels Week. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 529, National Drug Abuse Education and Prevention Week. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 437, National Employ the Older Worker Week. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 2847, National Employment Priorities Act. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 453, National High-Tech Week. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 2991, National Industrial Strategy Act. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 583, National Jerome Kern Day. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 606, National Housing Week. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 566, National Neighborhood Housing Services Week. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 392, National Pearl Harbor Remembrance Day. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 4245, National Professions and Technology Foundation Act of, 1983. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 544, National School-Age Child Care Awareness Week. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 7, National School Lunch Act and the Child Nutrition Act of, Amended., 1963 (Box 18)
      - H.Res. 155, National Sickle-Cell Anemia Awareness Month. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 478, National Week of the Ocean. (Box 18)
      - H.Res. 395, News Media to Refrain from Predicting Presidential Results Before Polls Close. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 100, Nondiscrimination in Insurance Act. (Box 18)
      - H.J.Res. 587, Ostomy Awareness Month. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 6225, Prevent Disruption of the Structure and Function of the Government. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 5586, Professional Development Resource Center Act of, 1984. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 5143, Public Employees Pension Plan Reporting and Accountability Act of, 1984. (Box 18)
      - H.Res. 473, Public Telephone Service. (Box 18)
      - H.R. 5745, Reproductive Health Equity Act. (Box 19)
      - H.R. 3348, Leo J. Ryan Medal. (Box 19)
      - H.R. 3331, Santa Monica Mountains National Recreation Area. (Box 19)
      - H.R. 4193, School Facilities Child Care Act. (Box 19)
      - H.R. 5749, Secondary School Basic Skills Act. (Box 19)
      - H.Res. 548, Select Committee on Cities. (Box 19)
      - H.Res. 16, Select Committee on Children, Youth, and Families. (Box 19)
      - H.R. 5525, Semiconductor Chip Protection Act of, 1984. (Box 19)
      - H.Con.Res. 333, Senior Companion Program. (Box 19)
      - H.J.Res. 603, Father Junipero Serra Day. (Box 19)
      - H.R. 2133, Small Business Act, Amended. (Box 19)
      - H.J.Res. 555, Space Exploration Day. (Box 19)
      - H.R. 3366, Telecommunications Competition Act of, 1983. (Box 19)
      - H.R. 3365, Telecommunications Regulations Reform Act of, 1983. (Box 19)
      - H.R. 4447, Temporary Suspension of Deportation of Certain Nationals of El Salvador. (Box 19)
      - H.R. 4908, Title 11 of the U.S. Code, Amended. (Box 19)
      - H.R. 5232, Truth in Savings Act. (Box 19)
      - H.R. 1249, U.S. Academy of Peace and Conflict Resolution Act. (Box 19)
      - H.J.Res. 429, U.S.-People's Republic of China Student Exchange. (Box 19)
      - H.R. 3108, United States Caribbean Possessions Act. (Box 19)
      - H.Con.Res. 100, Urging Soviet union to End Current Repressive Policies of Forced Labor. (Box 19)
      - H.R. 4772, Vietnam Veterans of America, Incorporated, Federal Charter. (Box 19)
      - H.R. 5762, Voting Accessibility for the Elderly and Handicapped Act. (Box 19)
      - H.R. 3795, Wine Equity Act of, 1983. (Box 19)
      - H.J.Res. 554, Women in Agriculture Week. (Box 19)
    - Education and Labor Committee Files
      - Education and Labor. (Box 19)
      - SubCommittee on Employment Opportunities. (Box 19)
      - Article (for Dr. Reissman) What Reagan is Doing to Us -- Minorities and Unemployment. (Box 19)
    - Committee Files
      - Agriculture Committee. (Box 19)
      - Appropriations Committee. (Box 19)
      - Armed Services Committee. (Box 19)
      - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs Committee. (Box 19)
      - Budget Committee. (Box 19)
      - Energy and Commerce Committee. (Box 19)
      - Foreign Affairs Committee. (Box 19)
      - Government Operations Committee. (Box 19)
      - House Administration Committee. (Box 19)
      - Interior and Insular Affairs Committee. (Box 19)
      - Judiciary Committee. (Box 19)
      - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee. (Box 19)
      - Post Office and Civil Service Committee. (Box 19)
      - Public Works and Transportation Committee. (Box 19)
      - Rules Committee. (Box 19)
      - Science and Technology Committee. (Box 19)
      - Standards of Official Conduct Committee. (Box 19)
      - Veterans' Affairs Committee. (Box 19)
      - Ways and Means Committee (2). (Box 19)
      - Select Committee on Narcotics Abuse and Control. (Box 19)
      - Joint Committee on Printing. (Box 19)
      - Joint Committee on the Library. (Box 19)
      - Joint Economic Committee. (Box 19)
  - 99th Congress (), 1985-86
    - Bills Sponsored
      - H.J.Res. 644, Adult Literacy Awareness Month. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 4154, Age Discrimination in Employment Amendments of, 1986. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 650, American Defense Education Act. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 5211, Authorization of the Appointment of Certain Additional Asst. Secretary of Labor. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 4143, Christa McAuliffe National Talented Teacher Fellowship Program. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 700, Civil Rights Restoration Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 670, Community Renewal Employment Act. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 4728, Education and Training for American Competitiveness Act. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 747*, Effective Schools Development in Education Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H. Res. 65, Expenses for SubCommittee on Labor Management for 1st Session, 99th Congress. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 4463, Effective Schools and Even Start Act. (Box 20)
      - H.Con.Res. 95, Head Start's 20th Anniversary. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 2907, Institutional Aid Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 5185, Job Training Partnership Amendments of, 1986. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 32, Minority Institutions Science Improvement Program. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 5607, National Fund for Literacy Development Act. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 7, National School Lunch and Child Nutrition Act of, Extended and Improved., 1966 (Box 20)
      - H.Res. 64, Operating Expenses for Education and Labor Committee for 1st Session, 99th Congress. (Box 20)
      - H.Res. 268, Opposing Taxation of Fringe Benefits. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 925, Pension Plan South African Investment Reporting Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 2840, School Excellence and Reform Act. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 926, South African Labor Relations Reform Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 4986, Work Incentive Amendments of, 1986. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 671, Youth Incentive Employment Act. (Box 20)
    - Bills Cosponsored
      - H.R. 4567, Acid Deposition Control Act of, 1986. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 927, Adolescent Pregnancy and Parenthood Act of, 1984. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 1279, Aid to Families with Dependent Children, Amended. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 524, Alzheimer's Disease and Related Disorders Treatment Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 99, American Conservation Corps Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 1460, Anti-Apartheid Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.Res. 564, Apology from Prime Minister of Japan. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 1400, Authorization of Appropriations for 5 Years Extended. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 1855, Automobile Consumer Protection Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 2867, Child Care Opportunities and Families Act. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 1906, Child Nutrition Act of, Amended., 1966 (Box 20)
      - H.R. 442, Civil Liberties Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 230, Civil Rights Amendments Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 3085, Clear Title to Certain Lands Along the California-Nevada Boundary. (Box 20)
      - H.Con.Res. 139, Commission to Study Compensation and Other Personnel Policies in Legislative Branch. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 5554, Community Development Credit Union Revolving Loan Fund Transfer Act. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 4421, Community Services Programs Amendments of, 1986. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 1856, Comprehensive Nutrition Assistance Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 281, Construction Industry Labor Law Amendments of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 4060, Amend U.S. Code, re Provide Full Cost-of-Living Adjustments. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 3042, Dropout Prevention and Reentry Act of, 1986. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 4323, Amend the Fair Labor Standards Act of, 1938. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 1297, Economic Growth Zone Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.Res. 239, Economic Sanctions Against South African Government. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 5520, Education of the Handicapped Act Amendments of, 1986. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 5136, Education, Job Training, and Youth Shelters for the Homeless Act. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 3326, Education Technology Act. (Box 20)
      - H.Res. 258, Educational Consideration, Internal Revenue Code. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 1356, Employee Educational Assistance Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 1809, End Use of Steel Jaw Leghold Traps. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 5042, English Proficiency Act. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 1575, Equal Credit Opportunity Act, Amended. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 2443, Expedited Funds Availability Act. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 501, Export Administration Act of, Amended., 1979 (Box 20)
      - H.J.Res. 188, Fair Housing Month. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 5614, Fair Labor Standards Act of, Amended., 1938 (Box 20)
      - H.R. 3530, Fair Labor Standards Amendments of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 4412, Fair Trade and Economic Justice Act. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 5165, Federal Equal Employment Opportunity Reporting Act of, 1986. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 3008, Federal Equitable Pay Practices Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.Con.Res. 34, re Federal Home Loan Bank Board. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 3048, Foreign Language Assistance for National Security Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 822, GAO Investigation and Report of Displaced Salvadorans. (Box 20)
      - H.Res. 155, Marianne Mele Hall Resignation. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 1978, Hazardous Waste Safety and Technology Incentive Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 3700, Higher Education Amendments of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 1309, High Risk Occupational Disease Notification and Prevention Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 3204, Home Equity Conversions Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 5140, Homeless Person's Survival Act of, 1986. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 882, Housing and Community Development Act of, Amended., 1974 (Box 20)
      - H.R. 4990, Hunger Relief Act of, 1986. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 2247, Impoundment Control Act of, Amended., 1974 (Box 20)
      - H.R. 1398, Income and Jobs Action Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 2908, Indian Education Technical Amendments Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 1145, Information Dissemination and Research Accountability Act. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 1458, Internal Revenue Code, Amended. (Box 20)
      - H.Res. 72, Job Corps Program. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 1616, Labor Management Notification and Consultation Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.J.Res. 664, Let Freedom Ring Day. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 4422, Low-Income Home Energy Assistance Act. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 4696, Manufacture and Public Distribution of Certain Copyrighted Material Act. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 2659, Medical Malpractice Reform Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 4287, Medicare Part C: Catastrophic Health Insurance Act of, 1986. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 1801, Medicare Solvency and Health Care Financing Reform Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.J.Res. 345, Music in Our Schools Month. (Box 20)
      - H.J.Res. 170, National Asthma and Allergy Awareness Week. (Box 20)
      - H.J.Res. 698, National Back to School - Back Off Drugs Month. (Box 20)
      - H.J.Res. 79, National Children's Week. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 615, National Commission on Neurofibromatosis Act. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 10, National Development Investment Act. (Box 20)
      - H.J.Res. 358, National Drunk and Drugged Driving Awareness Week. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 5526, The National Ground Water Contamination Research Act of, 1986. (Box 20)
      - H.J.Res. 74, National Independent Retail Grocer Week. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 2021, National Nehemiah Housing Opportunity Act. (Box 20)
      - H.J.Res. 492, National Neighborhood Housing Services Week. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 3997, National Policy and Technology Foundation Act of, 1985. (Box 20)
      - H.J.Res. 505, National Teacher Recognition Day. (Box 20)
      - H.R. 3090, Occupational Disease Compensation Act of, 1985. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 5179, Office of Civil Rights Assessment Act of, 1986. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 5484, Omnibus Drug Enforcement, Education, and Control Act of, 1986. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 4300, Parental and Medical Leave Act of, 1986. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 5668, Pension Restoration Act of, 1986. (Box 21)
      - H.J.Res. 428, Prohibit Sales of Advanced Weapons to Jordan. (Box 21)
      - H.J.Res. 589, Prohibit Sales of Certain Missiles to Saudi Arabia. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 3127, H.R. 3126, Public Employee Pension Plan Reporting and Accountability Act of (2)., 1985 (Box 21)
      - H.R. 4021, Rehabilitation Act Amendments of, 1986. (Box 21)
      - H.Res. 373, Resolution Regarding South Africa. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 749, Schoolbus Safety Belts, New Buses. (Box 21)
      - H.Res. 20, Establish a Select Committee on Hunger. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 2558, Leslie N. Shaw, Sr. General Mail. (Box 21)
      - Facility of the U.S. Postal Service. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 2860, Social Security Act, Amended. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 1917, Social Security Act, Amended, re Notch. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 526, State and Local Narcotics Control Assistance Act of, 1985. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 776, Study Duplicative Collection by Department of Health and Human Services. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 1099, Teenage Suicide Prevention Program Grants. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 3800, Telecommunications Equipment and Information Services Act of, 1985. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 948, Tenants' Protection Act of, 1985. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 1562, Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act of, 1985. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 2848, Transportation on Air Carriers Serving Alcoholic Beverages. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 2282, Truth in Savings Act. (Box 21)
      - H.J.Res. 437, Urban Mass Transportation Administration. (Box 21)
      - U.S. Code, Amended
        - H.R. 3174, Amend Chapter 171, re Armed Forces to Sue for Damages from Improper Medical Care. (Box 21)
        - H.R. 2851, re Benefits for Certain Government Workers. (Box 21)
        - H.R. 917, re Title 5. (Box 21)
        - H.R. 2854, re Postal Service. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 4821, U.S. Institute of Peace. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 858, Veteran's Administration Adjudication Procedure and Judicial Review Act. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 1304, War Powers Act. (Box 21)
      - H.J.Res. 499, Women's History Week. (Box 21)
      - H.R. 4650, Youth Suicide Prevention Act. (Box 21)
    - Education and Labor Committee Files
      - Education and Labor Committee (2). (Box 21)
      - John Williams' Folder. (Box 21)
      - Education and Labor Newsletter. (Box 21)
    - Committee Files
      - Agriculture Committee. (Box 21)
      - Appropriations Committee. (Box 21)
      - Armed Services Committee. (Box 21)
      - Banking, Finance, and Urban Affairs Committee. (Box 21)
      - Budget Committee. (Box 21)
      - Energy and Commerce Committee. (Box 21)
      - Foreign Affairs Committee. (Box 21)
      - Government Operations Committee. (Box 21)
      - House Administration Committee. (Box 21)
      - Interior and Insular Affairs Committee. (Box 21)
      - Judiciary Committee. (Box 22)
      - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee. (Box 22)
      - Post Office and Civil Service Committee. (Box 22)
      - Public Works and Transportation Committee. (Box 22)
      - Rules Committee. (Box 22)
      - Veterans' Affairs Committee. (Box 22)
      - Ways and Means Committee (2). (Box 22)
      - Select Committee on Aging. (Box 22)
      - Select Committee on Children, Youth, and Families. (Box 22)
      - Select Committee on Hunger. (Box 22)
      - Select Committee on Narcotics Abuse and Control. (Box 22)
      - Joint Economic Committee. (Box 22)
      - Joint Committee on Inaugural Ceremonies. (Box 22)
      - Joint Committee on Printing. (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence. (Box 22)
  - 99th-100th Congress, Miscellaneous
    - Legislative Profile, 99th-101st Session. (Box 128)
    - Human Rights Legislative Profile, 100th-102nd. (Box 128)
    - List of Legislation, 99th-100th Congresses (2). (Box 128)
  - 101st Congress (), 1989-90
    - Legislative Profile, 101st-1st. (Box 128)
    - Cosponsors and Dear Colleagues. (Box 128)
    - List of Legislation (notebook). (Box 134)
    - Legislative Files, 101st Congress
      - Committee Files. (Box 129)
      - Bills Sponsored. (Box 129)
      - Bills Cosponsored. (Box 129)
      - Bills Cosponsored. (Box 130)
      - Legislative Assistant Files
        - Mary Luevano's Files, 1988-90. (Box 130)
        - Gail Perry's Files, 1985-90. (Box 131)
  - Miscellaneous Committee Files
    - House Administration Committee, 1979-84. (Box 22)
      - House Information Systems. (Box 22)
      - Task Force. (Box 22)
      - Personnel (2). (Box 22)
      - Organizing the Committee Reading File. (Box 22)
      - HIS 1981 Budget (notebook) Loose Materials. (Box 22)
      - Report of the Task Force on Enforcement (notebook). (Box 23)
    - Joint Committee on the Library, 1981-82. (Box 23)
    - Joint Committee on Printing, 1980-81. (Box 23)
      - Joint Committee on Printing. (Box 23)
      - Appropriations Hearing, Fiscal Year, Representative Hawkins (notebook)., 1982 (Box 23)
  - Legislative Files (To Be Interfiled)
    - Proposed Legislation, 88th-92nd. (Box 80)
    - Select Committee on U.S. Involvement in Southeast Asia, 1970. (Box 80)
    - Extend Authorization for Cabinet Committee on Opportunities for Spanish Speaking People, October 1973. (Box 80)
    - Legislative Files (To Be Interfiled)
      - Legislation Cosponsored
        - 1983. (Box 81)
        - 1983-84. (Box 81)
        - (2)., 1984 (Box 81)
        - 1985-88. (Box 81)
- Subject Files, 1965-90; (Contained in 31 Boxes)